ecochunk.com 2013-12-21

# EcoChunk Privacy Policy | Eco Chunk

The site is controlled and operated by EcoChunk from India, and is not intended to subject to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the India. EcoChunk does not represent or warrant that the Site or any part thereof is appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the site do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations.

By using the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy, please do not use the site. We reserve the right to change this Policy without prior notice. Any changes to our Policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Policy on the Internet, accessible through the site.

### **EcoChunk respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of EcoChunk.

**Credit card details**

EcoChunk will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on EcoChunk.

**External Sites.**

EcoChunk is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. EcoChunk may contain links to third party web sites. These linked sites (including without limitation the web sites of Affiliated Entities) are not under EcoChunk’s control and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of any such linked site, or any link contained in any linked site. We provide such links only as a convenience, and the inclusion of a link on EcoChunk does not imply endorsement of the linked site by EcoChunk or any Affiliated Entities.

**Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows EcoChunk to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and EcoChunk does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to EcoChunk and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through EcoChunk have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:thechunkmedia@gmail.com)

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, please contact us either by e-mail at thechunkmedia[at]gmail.com, or by regular mail at 34, Gopi Cottage, Kasumpti, Shimla- 171009, H.P., India . Please note that e-mail communications will not necessarily be secure; accordingly you should not include credit card information or other sensitive information in your e-mail correspondence with us.

### Share and Enjoy
